{
    "subject": "Olga_Havlov\u00e1",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "V\u00e1clav_Havel",
    "human_readable": "Olga Havlov\u00e1 is married to V\u00e1clav Havel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883715510368347,
            "question": "Is V\u00e1clav Havel married to Olga Havlov\u00e1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9836392998695374,
            "question": "Is V\u00e1clav Havel's spouse named Olga Havlov\u00e1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.967103123664856,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Olga Havlov\u00e1 and V\u00e1clav Havel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.946974515914917,
            "question": "Who is Olga Havlov\u00e1 in relation to V\u00e1clav Havel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9286327362060547,
            "question": "To whom was Olga Havlov\u00e1 married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9279309511184692,
            "question": "Who is Olga Havlov\u00e1 married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9232051968574524,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Olga Havlov\u00e1 and V\u00e1clav Havel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9135702848434448,
            "question": "Name the spouse of V\u00e1clav Havel."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.727298378944397,
            "question": "Who is Olga Havlov\u00e1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46720874309539795,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the personal life of V\u00e1clav Havel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olga Havlov\u00e1 is married to V\u00e1clav Havel.",
            "html": "yago_31053_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Olga Havlov\u00e1?",
            "html": "yago_31053_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the spouse of V\u00e1clav Havel.",
            "html": "yago_31053_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Olga Havlov\u00e1 and V\u00e1clav Havel?",
            "html": "yago_31053_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31053_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents clearly state that Olga Havlov\u00e1 was previously married to V\u00e1clav Havel, and there is no contradictory information provided. Therefore, the triple is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Olga Havlov\u00e1 was previously married to V\u00e1clav Havel and that they were married in 1964, making the statement \"Olga Havlov\u00e1 is married to V\u00e1clav Havel\" correct according to the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}